millionairesociety.com 2017-12-01

# Millionaire Society | Privacy Policy

Epicenter Enterprises, LLC  
Privacy Policy

Effective January 01, 2015

www.MillionaireSociety.com (the "Site") is owned and operated by Epicenter Enterprises, LLC (the "Company"). By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of your information by us in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Do not use the Site if you do not agree with this Privacy Policy.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how the Site collects information from all end users of our Internet services ("Services"), including those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors"), as well as those who may purchase products and/or pay a monthly fee to subscribe to our Services ("Members"). This Privacy Policy also describes what we do with the information we collect, and the choices that Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of such information. We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

Changes to the Privacy Policy  
We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. Since any changes will be posted on this page, we encourage you to check this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes.Personal Information We Collect and How It Is Used

We may collect personally identifiable information from you such as your name, postal address, telephone number, fax number and email address ("Personally Identifiable Information"). We will collect Personally Identifiable Information from you when you actively give us the information, such as when you order or purchase products or Services, register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, or otherwise communicate with the Site.

Service Providers: When you become a Member, purchase products or Services, or use other features on the Site, we request that you provide financial information, such as account or credit card numbers ("Financial Information"). We will use your financial information to bill you for products and Services and otherwise process your transactions. By making a purchase on the Site, you consent to our sharing your Personally Identifiable Information and Financial Information with our service providers and to such third parties as we determine is necessary to process your transactions, including, Clickbank.com. These third parties may include credit card companies and banking institutions used to process the transaction. We contractually prohibit these third parties from using your Personally Identifiable Information for any other purpose. We may use third party contractors to help us operate our business and administer activities on our behalf, such as authorization of credit card transactions, and may share your information with these contractors for those limited purposes.Online Shopping: At some Web sites described within our Site, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter. You can decide whether or not to use these sites or services at your own discretion. There is also the likely chance that the Company will receive compensation for any purchases you make from any websites recommended by the Company.Newsletters: If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your email address to send the newsletter to you. We require that you "Opt-in" in order to receive our newsletter. Choice/Opt-out: We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of receiving our newsletter, in which case your email address is permanently removed from our database. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, you may opt-out of receiving it by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

We may use your Personally Identifiable Information to contact you with information we think you would be interested in. If you do not want to receive this information, email us at support(at)millionairesociety.com. Email messages will also provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of receiving this information. Please note that changes to your preferences may not be effective immediately.

Testimonials: If you submit a testimonial, you should be aware that any Personally Identifiable Information you submit, such as your name, Web site, city and/or country of residence may be displayed on our Site, where it could potentially be used by third parties to contact you, or send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personally Identifiable Information you choose to submit in a testimonial.

Third Party Marketing: The Comapny may sell your Personally Identifiable Information or share with our third party marketing partners.Your Personally Identifiable Information will be used by our third party marketing partners to offer you goods and services that our third party marketing partners deem closely related to your interest in the Company's products and services. If you do not agree to this policy please do not sumbit your Personally Identifiable Information to the Company. If you do not wish to ever ben contacted by the Company or our third party marketing partners you may place yourself on the Company's global DoNotContact list by visiting the following website: http://www.millionairesociety.com/unsubscribe/

California Privacy Rights: Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a customer and a California resident, you may request information about our company's disclosure of your personal data to third parties. To receive this information, please write to the following address: e-mail support(at)millionairesociety.com

"Non-personally Identifiable Information" and How We Use It: We may collect non-personally identifiable information such as your Web Site browsing patterns, IP address and demographic information, such as your zip code and income level ("Non-personally Identifiable Information"). We use this Non-personally Identifiable Information to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. We may also share Non-personally Identifiable Information in the aggregate form with third parties to illustrate trends and patterns. We collect Non-personally Identifiable Information from you by "passive" means, often through the use of cookies. In addition, on occasion, the Site may also set a "session cookie" to help us administer the Site. A session cookie expires when you close your browser and does not retain any information about you after it expires. 

If you are a Visitor or Member we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Web sites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. Advertisers and marketing partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

Legal: If Company is sold to, or merges with, another company, or declares bankruptcy, some or all of the information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of the transfer of assets. We reserve the right to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site, or to protect our company and our Members.Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. This Site is not intended for use by children. We will not knowingly collect any Personally Identifiable Information submitted by visitors to the Site who are under the age of 13.

Our Commitment to Data Security

The Site and our Services have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized third-parties from illegally obtaining this information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

Links  
The Site may contain links to other sites, including, among others, those of advertisers, other third parties and companies whose trademarks may appear on the Site. We are not responsible for the information collection practices or the content of the sites to which we link.Community Functions

The Site may make available to Visitors and Members chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or other community functions. Remember that any information you disclose in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personally Identifiable Information, Financial Information, or other information. You should use community functions at your own risk.

Contact Us

If you have questions about our Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us at:

email:

support(at)millionairesociety.com

Or via mail at the following:

Epicenter Enterprises, LLC  
2081 Center Street   
Berkeley, CA 94704 

Effective Date: March 9, 2011*NOTICE* \- Anyone who distributes illegal copies of our program, or uses our trademarked/copyrighted Epicenter Enterprises. LLC text and/or images without permission will be reported to their billing and/or hosting company, and any other related companies for account closure. We will follow with a federal copyright infringement lawsuit in accordance with the The Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). 

The entire contents of this website is Copyright © 2011 by MillionaireSociety.com. All rights reserved. This site may not be copied in whole or in part without the express written permission of the publisher. All violators will be prosecuted to the fullest extent of the law.
